Law...
Go...
My real name is...
Trafalgar D. Water Law.
Is that a secret?
Yes.
I'm surprised. So you have
a D. in your name, too.
I'm telling you because I trust you.
Thank you.
But... I don't have any answers for you.
Luffy might not care,
but personally...
I want to learn the meaning of D., too.
So all we can do is follow the red stones?
Indeed...
And that means toppling the Four Emperors.
It's not as if they'll just
hand them over, after all.
This isn't it...
It needs to be red.
In some places, the people
of the D. have been called...
"the Natural Enemies of the Gods!"
Hey, Cora...
I still wanna know...
why I have to lead...
such a checkered life.
Usopp! Are you okay?!
Who d'ya think I am?!
I'm most certainly not okay...
No, you most certainly aren't...
But at the very least, I am.
Seriously?
Hey, Otama. How did you get here?
One of the enemies gave me a boat ride!
What?! An enemy?!
Pay-Pay! Chew that dog up!
Do it yourself!
Damn! What's with this baboon?!
Wherever did he come from?!
Hihimaru!
Keep them busy for three minutes!
Those two mean business!
That giant monkey will get hurt!
Don't underestimate us, Onami!
We came here...
as samurai!
Get out of my way!
We can do this forever, Young Master Yamato.
Although, I can't go losing any more
of my impregnable Armored Division.
How dare you harm so many of them?!
Aim!
Fire!
Momonosuke! Shinobu!
Yamato...
If you keep taking bullets...
This is nothing.
If you are a samurai, then you must decide!
Leave me here and take Lord Momonosuke...
No!
If it were Oden...
If it were Kozuki Oden...
he would never do that!
How stubborn...
Do you really think you can defeat me
while you're fretting over those weaklings?
What arrogance, Young Master Yamato!
Sasaki...
What just happened?!
Outta my way! Outta my way!
Get outta my way!
Franosuke!
Huh? Momo?!
Good to see you alive and kicking!
Shinobu, you doing okay there?!
That's...
I know him! He's part of Luffy's crew!
Cyborg Franky! He's worth 94 million berries!
It's hard to believe he's real!
Haccha?! Why are you here?!
Oh no, not good!
Don't you dare, dumbass!
Is this because you couldn't
catch me?! How childish!
Armored Division! Don't lose them!
Keep them from running at any cost!
He broke the floor!
Oh, right! There's a floor beneath us!
Momonosuke! Shinobu!
Let's make our way down like this!
Momo! Shinobu! Are you okay?!
Did you get caught?!
No! This is an ally!
Cyborg Franky! I'll leave the enemy to you!
Who are you?!
Luffy entrusted these two to me!
I don't know who you are...
but I got it! You can super count on me!
Shinobu, take Momonosuke!
What?
I wanna return a favor!
I'll be right back!
I gotta take him down at least...
Narikabura Arrow!
Alright!
That stranger did this?!
Who was that?
Haccha?!
Dammit!
Yamato took Momonosuke down that hole!
Organize a pursuit unit! Chase after them now!
Armored Division!
Let's deal with the damn robot!
Momonosuke!
You must survive!
Survive at any cost!
The one who'll lead the world to a new dawn...
is you!
Kaido!
How annoying!
You've already lost, you fools!
She's coming!
Big Mom is back!
Don't worry! I'm only interested in going...
up to where Kaido is.
I know how to fight the virus!
You do?!
Run, Apoo!
You'd better not let this show end just yet!
Omasa!
Hey! Come to your senses!
There's no other option, huh?
No... I've finally made it this far...
I don't want to die here!
Please, help me...
He's still on my tail!
What a pain! He won't give it a rest!
Apoo!
Give me the antibody!
Drake, you bastard!
You're here! Back me up!
What are you doing?!
We gotta fight him together!
Damn you!
Like I said, it isn't fair to fight me as a duet!
He wants a solo against me!
Isn't that right?!
Beats me what's going on here.
I didn't expect you to be so chill with it!
Alright, then... Check it out!
What?!
Hey! Zoro!
Oh, Chopper.
Thanks!
Can I leave this floor to you?
I can't stay for the show.
You'll live, right?
Of course!
I've already figured out how the virus works!
That's my guy!
Is he gonna gather all the metal in the castle?!
Dammit!
Eustass Captain Kid!
Stop him! Don't let him get to the rooftop!
They're coming.
Let me greet them...
with this overwhelming amount of mass!
It's fine if you don't move outta
the way. Just come right to us!
Do you think this is enough, Killer?!
Our enemy is the world's strongest pirate...
You can never have too much.
You said it!
Stop Straw Hat!
What floor are we on?!
We're coming up on the third floor!
The rooftop is above the fifth floor!
Alright! Kin'emon, wait for me!
That's...
Hey! Do you guys hear that?
Huh? Hear what?
Oh no... It's coming from the third floor!
Whaddya say? Whaddya say?
Please don't!
I need it!
You ought not!
How naughty!
Wait for us, Kin'emon!
Which way is the rooftop?!
That way!
Alright!
Whaddya say? Whaddya say?
You ought not! You ought not!
How naughty!
I have something serious to attend to.
You guys, go ahead!
I'll catch up as soon as I'm done!
I hear it!
How naughty!
A beautiful woman...
is calling for help!
How naughty!
That's it, come here!
Oh, you ought not do this!
You're a real cutie, so whaddya say?
You ought not!
Whaddya say?
You really ought not!
Please stop!
How naughty!
Samurai-style sexual harassment!
"Whaddya say?", "How naughty!"
How naughty!
Someone in a position of power is
untying a helpless woman's kimono.
What the spinning woman
loses with each turn...
isn't just her dress!
It's her dignity!
Just hold on! Help is on the way!
Whaddya...?
It's not right!
Stop it!
What?! What's this?!
How naughty!
A spider web?!
Hey, stop that!
How naughty!
– Naughty Trap!
Another perv in shining armor came...
Damn... It was a trap...
Black Leg Sanji of the Straw Hat Pirates.
He's worth 330 million berries!
Probably competing with his crewmate Zoro.
I think this one's bounty is higher.
Wow! We caught some big game!
Untie me now and I'll let this slide!
Oh, how scary! You're blackmailing us!
I have somewhere to be!
If you go, the battlefield will just spill over.
And I don't want this banquet
hall to be caught up in it.
My allies are waiting for me!
Untie the damn rope already!
Boys with dirty mouths get me all tingly.
"Boy"?! Stop messing with me!
Hey... what do you say?
Do you...
like me?
Cut it out! I don't...
I don't like you...
I love you!
Hey, Gorishiro! You're getting banana on me!
Master Poker! Straw Hat and Jinbe
are heading your way!
Yeah, got it.
Regrettably, I let Kid through...
But look! Straw Hat's bounty
is 1.5 billion berries!
Taking him down will do more
than just clear my name!
Aw, man! Come on!
Me, in the Soaring Six? That'll do nicely.
Straw Hat! Straw Hat!
This way!
Who are they?
Oh, it's you guys!
The ones from Udon!
Hey, Straw Hat isn't here yet?!
He should be there soon!
A ladder...
Yeah, you can climb
to the fourth floor with this.
A bunch of enemies are waiting at the stairs.
That helps a lot. Thanks!
Where is he?!
Everyone, listen up!
Use fire against the ice ogres!
This virus fuses with
the gas that's chilling our bodies!
Look at me!
If you stop the chill, the virus can't multiply!
Meanwhile, I'll make enough
antibodies for everyone!
I'm a doctor! I'll save everyone,
both allies and enemies!
– What?!
Everyone?! Including Omasa?!
So stay alive! Don't let
that horrible man kill you!
How nice, tanuki!
And you're pathetic, Apoo!
I presented you with such
a fun little ogre game...
and you just had to go and ruin it!
You two have gotten on my last nerve!
What?!
Screw the game!
What?
I didn't come to this island
to play around with you losers!
I came to chop up Kaido...
the so-called strongest man in the world!
What?!
His anger triggered an earthquake?!
Was that conqueror's haki?!
Hold on to something!
Everyone, hang in there!
Zoro, what did you do?!
I can't believe you did this!
There's no way that was me.
What's with this shaking?!
I'm scared!
No, I'm not scared!
You'll be fine! Just keep moving forward!
Let's hurry up!
What's this?! Is it an earthquake, Jinbe?!
Geologically speaking,
this island is unique, but...
It's no use! We can't reach the shore!
Let's pull away from Onigashima for now!
What the...
How impatient...
Is the island sinking?!
Onigashima's... What the hell is going on?!
Do you think the captain is okay?!
Momonosuke! Your survival
is the highest priority!
Let's board a ship and get out of here!
We've gotta hurry.
I have a bad feeling about this!
What was that?
It stopped shaking.
I know how you feel, Zoro... I saw it, too.
Okiku's arm!
Me as well!
I'm late to the party.
I wish I could just fly there.
But every route has its challenges.
Straw Hats!
Marco the Phoenix!
Yep, the one and only!
You guys are the VIPs!
Why are you still slumming it down here?
It's not like we want to be.
Is there anything I can do to help?
The Beast Pirates' ships... They're gone!
What?!
So is the sea!
What?! What do you mean by that?!
It's too late!
We can no longer flee to the sea!
Is this not a port?!
That quake before...
I get it now!
What is going on, Yamato?!
Dragons fly through the air
by creating flame clouds!
That means that right now...
Kaido is making Onigashima fly!
He's gonna relocate
the island to the Flower Capital!
N-No way...
Are you satisfied now?
The Kozuki are finished.
Wano, or more accurately, New Onigashima,
will become a stronghold for pirates.
Let's usher in a world of violence!